"data": [
    {
      "question": "The older one is ___ of the two clerks.",
      "a": "patienter",
      "b": "more patient",
      "c": "the most patient",
      "d": "the more patient",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": ".\n- Comprative: used when comparing two things\n+ adj + er (short adj)/ more + adj (long adj)\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "16",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "After the new equipment was introduced, the factory produced ___ kitchenware this year as the year before.",
      "a": "as much twice",
      "b": "as twice much",
      "c": "twice much as",
      "d": "twice as much",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": ". \n- Twice as much= double",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "16",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The earth is ___ the moon.",
      "a": "forty-nine times bigger than",
      "b": "as big as forty-nine times",
      "c": "bigger forty-nine times than",
      "d": "forty-nine times as bigger as",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": ".\n- Comparative: number + comparative adjective",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "16",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "This reservoir is ___ that one.",
      "a": "one-fourth as big as",
      "b": "one-fourth time as big as",
      "c": "one-fourth times the size of",
      "d": "as big as one-fourth",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Comparative: number + comparative adjective",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "16",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am two years ___ than he.",
      "a": "less",
      "b": "smaller",
      "c": "younger",
      "d": "more",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": ".\n- Comparative: number + comparative adjective",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "16",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The book seems to be ___ like a comic ___ a dictionary.",
      "a": "much, than",
      "b": "more, than",
      "c": "very, than",
      "d": "many, than",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- More...than: [used before an adjective or adverb to form the comparative] having a particular quality to a greater degree",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "16",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It's never ___ to learn.",
      "a": "to late",
      "b": "late enough to",
      "c": "very late",
      "d": "too late",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": ".\n- Too adj/adv+ to do sth: more than is acceptable or possible",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "16",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Open your mouth ___.",
      "a": "widely",
      "b": "wide",
      "c": "more wide",
      "d": "large",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Open/spread (something) wide (adv)....",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "16",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "When the doctor entered the ward, he found his patient became ___ awake.",
      "a": "much",
      "b": "very",
      "c": "quite",
      "d": "wide",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Wide open/awake/apart/: completely open, awake, or apart",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "16",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The road is not ___ for two cars to pass side by side.",
      "a": "wide enough",
      "b": "enough wide",
      "c": "wide",
      "d": "so wide",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": ".",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "16",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]